

Mykola Hryshchenko Software Engineer (Python)

SAVE

Mobile +38(066)9609136 github.com/nyckolas-python linkedin.com/in/nyckolas-python email: nyckolas.python@gmail.com

SKILLS

Backend:

[Python, Flask, Django, Pandas, PandaSQL]

Databases:

[PostgreSQL, LiteSQL]

DevOps:

[GIT, Docker, Bash]

TRAININGS & COURSES

Hexlet:

[Python Developer]

Hexlet:

[PostgreSQL]

Udemy:

[Docker]

LANGUAGES

English:

intermediate

Ukrainian:

as a native language

Russian:

as a native language

STRENGTHS

Learning

Eager to learn as much as possible about Python and software development

SUMMARY

Entry level Python developer with a strong background experience in marketing and business processing. 1,5+ years experience with Python. My strongest skills is database management with Python.

I'm hard-working web developer with a flair for creating elegant solution. I am looking for a company willing to offer me a placement among their developers. In return, I would offer my full commitment, and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team.

EXPERIENCE

[202 - 2022]

Self Employed • Python Software Engineer • Freelancer

I used **Django** and **Flask** to create sites, **aiogram** was a tool for creating bots. Also had working experience with **PostgreSQL**, **Pandas**, **SQLite**. Deployed projects on Heroku. Familiar with AWS, CI/CD, Docker, SOLID. I've been programming every day for about 1,5+ years.

[2019 - 2021]

YOUCAN • Founder • PM

This was my own e-commerce project.

- IMPORTANT For the first time in a long time I used my skills in programming, which determined the change in the vector of my activity.
- Gained invaluable experience and improved project management skills.
- Worked a lot with freelancers, drew up technical specifications and monitored the completion of tasks.

[2012 - 2018]

Megastyle • Head of Sales Department •

While working at Megastyle, my way up from manager to head of the sales department.

- Opening of 5 retail stores.
- Interviews and hiring, training, adaptation of more than 30 employees.
- Description and implementation of business processes.
- Implementation of customer service automation CRM Bitrix24
- Opening of a branch in the capital of Ukraine Kyiv.



STRENGTHS

Time Management
I completed 2 Python courses successfully while combining full time work on my own ecom project.

I independently set tasks for myself, based on the needs and goals of the project, choose tools, estimate deadlines and meet them.

Commitment

I got out of my comfort zone and and left my secure job to pursue something i am interesting in. I committed to fully change my career and become an experienced Python developer.

EDUCATION

[2021 – 2022] Hexlet.io

- Python Developer
- PostgreSQL
- Flask
- Acquaintance with Django

[2019] 3 months

UNIT School of Business

- Business model
- Strategy
- Marketing
- Sales
- Management
- Finance
- Team

[2007] - [2012]

Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics

Economic Cybernetics

- The main thing I learned is to study.
- CPA 4,2/5

[1996] - [2007]

Educational complex of secondary education

- graduated with a silver medal
- CPA 10,5 / 12

MY HOBBY

My hobbies are marathon running and playing football.

MY CONTACTS ONES MORE TIME



Mobile +38(066)9609136 github.com/nyckolas-python linkedin.com/in/nyckolas-python email: nyckolas.python@gmail.com